http://www.pmcq.qc.ca/en/privacy

Français|Sitemap
PMCQ
Menu
Home
Our ClubBackOur ClubPresident's MessageBoard MembersPast PresidentsHonorary MembersBy LawsCommunityMembershipEventsBackEventsEvent CalendarMonthly MeetingHoliday SoiréeSummer SocialPast Meetings and PhotosPast Meetings ArchiveContact UsAsk PAABPast Meetings ArchiveBackPast Meetings ArchiveMove your career forward!This year’s PMCQ season packs a punch!To Fund or Not to Fund: A Question of Ethics. Perspective of Payers, Patients and PharmaHow to navigate the changing HCP landscape: Addressing HCP needs in promotion, education, and informationIs Digital and Social Media “the Fix” for Your Marketing Mix?
The evolution from tactic to strategy in the Canadian pharmaceutical industryInfluencing with Integrity: Intention vs. ImpactStanding Out in a Sea of Generics: Succeeding in the Loss of Exclusivity EnvironmentPan-Canadian Drug Pricing Alliance: How will it unfold?Frontline Innovation: Empowering Patients to Manage Their Own HealthPharmacists: Expanded Scope of Practice Market Revolution?The Global Transformation of Pharma: A Prescription for CanadaBuilding Effective Partnerships for Optimal Patient CareThe media challenge! Maximizing ROI with ROM (Return On Media)Innovation Revolution: Ignite Innovation in Every Aspect of Your CompanyAre Private Sector Formularies Set to Align with Public?Career Life Cycle Management. What You Need to Do to Prepare for and Thrive in PharmaEvolution of the PAAB Code: Revisions to s6.5. The Digital Side of PAABIs Pharma a Four-Letter Word?Charting the Course for the Pharmaceutical IndustryJoin the Debate! Loss-of-Exclusivity (LoE) StrategiesThe Evolving Sales Force and its Implications for the Marketing Mix: What We Can Learn and Not Learn from Other IndustriesPAAB Wants You: Have Your Say in the PAAB Code ChangeThe Future of the Québec Provincial Biopharmaceutical StrategyThe PMCQ presents Trends in Private Payers:
The Impact on Access and Patient Assistance ProgramsThe New Reality of Rx Pharma and the Evolving Role of Marketing in our Industry. Can Brand Pharma Overcome a Changing Environment and Generics?Managing Change in the Canadian Pharmaceutical IndustryThe changing landscape in PharmacyKey Challenges Facing the Canadian Pharmaceutical IndustryThe Hidden Truth Behind Community ManagementInnovation in Turbulent TimesListen, hear & trustPlanting Seeds OnlinePharma’s Market Access: SWOT’s Up?Getting high on serviceLarry Smith Goes LongThe Art of the Long View:
The Future of Health Care & PharmaceuticalsLess good work, more great workDo Canadians really do it better?"As The World Turns"
A Talk of Sense and SensibilityMike Lipkin is full of itJust a regulatory guyArtful PersuasionPluck of the IrishPow is the New WowThe world according to DianeIs the Canadian Healthcare System on life support?Innovate or dieBoom, Bust & Echo: Profiting from the Demographic Shift in the 21st CenturySix million dollar mindsMarc Garneau – First Canadian Astronaut. Time (and space) for changeWe have seen the future and it is… hereWISDOM FROM THE GROUND UPToo stressed to laugh about it?Tough talk we all need to hearBranding gets cleared upDo your customers prefer you?The Importance of Corporate CultureNo margin for error, making it in today’s pharmaceutical marketAnxious about everythingSix Pixels of SeparationBill 102 and the Issues Facing IndustryPMCQ U Presents: Pharmaceutical Idol!IN VIVO- Montreal’s Life Science ClusterThe 21st Century Court JesterFinding BalanceSpeaking VisuallyChange, evolve or you don’t exist...Magnificence at WorkPretty simple stuff...Emerging Trends in Pharmaceutical Marketing. Gaining Advantage in a World of ChangeTeamwork Most Often Doesn’tWhy do Teams not Work? What Companies Should KnowLessons LearnedThe Future is in Life SciencesGender differences and how to make it work at workGender Differences in Management StylesSharma’s Most Important LessonsThe most important lessons life has taught meRussell Williams’s Vision for Rx&DMEET THE PREZTrust in a Time of SuspicionBoom, Bust and Echo: Profiting from the Demographic Shift in the 21st CenturyBoom Bust and Echo: Profiting from the Demographic Shift in the 21st CenturyOCTOBER 2004 POST MEETING EVALUATIONA Marriage of Sales and MarketingLinking Marketing to Sales: Why Strategies FailAn analysis of attitudes to the PMCQ and the services it offersThe Power of PRThe 22 Immutable Laws of BrandingThe rituals of visionary leaders: extraordinary strategies to lead the fieldTake the Guess Out of Guesswork to Optimize your Promotional MixCross-Border Shopping: Will Canada's Pharmaceutical Industry Survive?Promotion Mix Optimization - An Evidence-based ApproachWill Canada's Pharmaceutical Industry Survive?Emotional Intelligence: Moving from Knowledge to ActionEmotional Intelligence: Moving from Knowledge to ActionBack to school"Communicate Real Meaning", Rex Tells PoliticiansFive Humorous Steps to Effective CommunicationBadvertisingCreativity and innovative strategy: Surviving and thriving in a high-speed worldJust Brand ItEQ TestingA Prescription for Pharmaceutical Financial HealthInformation Overload: Taming The “Trojan Horse”Turning Practice Guidelines into Patient HealthStirring “Call to Action” on African AIDs Pandemic: LewisDifferentiate or DieToday’s Rules of Engagement in the Public Affairs Debate Preparation Means SurvivalWhen Shift Happens!Pharma Stocks Still Solid: KrawsInternet Medicine...Rx&D ON CANADA’S “INNOVATION AGENDA”Laborde Can’t Elude PAAB JabsA Laugh-Filled Evening with the Diminutive, Dynamic Andrée JettéLeadership in the New MillenniumLet's Play the Networking GameWhat's the Prognosis, Dr. Vietor?Building a Better BrandThe Future of Health Care in CanadaThomas WitschiThe Inside Scoop: Marketing Pharma in the 21st CenturyHockey Night in DorvalVietor has Left the BuildingOvercoming hurdles in a digital worldEngage patients and profits will followAlternative promotional models in pharma: do you have the right one?Turn the conversation aroundLet’s discuss what’s new at the PCPAA Clearer Vision of Our FutureHow to Present Effectively to an Audience of… Squirrels?The Right Place at the Right Time Happens a Lot More When You’re Out There Every DayBRANDING #YOUPharmacy-pharma synergyWhen change is a mountain, how do you make it to the top?CPD: Why Give a Dime?Are We Addressing Evolving Healthcare Practitioners' Needs?Yes, You Can Build Your Brand in a Commodity Industry!Let's make good health infectiousInnovating in a highly regulated environmentWhere Biotech Meets PharmaPurpose and ProfitFear of public speaking: How to make the best of itShift in the Private Payers LandscapeThe evolution of clinical trialsCaptains of Industry: A View from the Flight DeckMaster of Your Thoughts, Master of Your LifeChange your mind. Change your life.Get ready for artificial intelligence. It’s coming - and NOW!Propel Yourself into the Future!Leading a Team to VictoryPMPRB Changes: Industry Outlook and Impact – What You Should KnowImmuno-oncology: Changing the face of cancerEmpowerment for Life: Partnering with patient organizations for better healthcare outcomesRunning on Empty: Manage Your Energy, Manage Your Stress A reflection on digital pharma practicesHiring for the right fit: an inquisitive approach to hiringPatient Support Programs - Trending or TransformativeMARIJUANA MYTHS AND FACTS: The Future of Cannabis in the Pharmaceutical IndustryBetter Access with National Pharmacare: Reality or Illusion?Boosting Launch Trajectory: Lessons from 40 product launchesHow Empathy Can Transform Health CareFocus the Way Forward: Agents of ChangeOptimizing outcomes faster - togetherTransformation! What it means and how to drive itHow Electronic Medical Records are Transforming Clinical PracticeIndustry challenges in Canada and in Quebec - Innovative Medicine CanadaFuture of technology in life sciencesRecharge and reconnect!Recharge and reconnect! - PHASE llRecharge and reconnect! - PHASE lllSUPPLY CHAIN MANAGEMENT: THE BACKBONE OF OUR INDUSTRYBiosimilars: The World Turned Upside DownVideos
Data Privacy Policy
The Pharmaceutical Marketing Club of Quebec recognizes and respects the privacy interest of individuals with regard to personal information provided to us.
How do we use this personal information?
Personal information collected by us through the P.M.C.Q. Online Meeting Reservation Form will only be used to respond to your request.
How do we safeguard personal information?
The Pharmaceutical Marketing Club of Quebec uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window.
Your consent
By providing personal information to us, you consent to the collection and use of the personal information in accordance with the purposes described in this privacy statement.
SUBSCRIBE
Sign up to the PMCQ email communications
Information
Tuesday, December 15, 2020
GENDER DISPARITY IN CLINICAL HEALTH RESEARCH
Virtual Meeting
Time: 12:00 p.m. - 1:00 p.m.
Online only!
RSVP:
Engage Presentations Inc.
Monthly Meeting »
Holiday Soirée 2019 »
Summer Social 2019 »
This site is maintained by Engage Presentations Inc.
Data Privacy Policy
© PMCQ 2006 - 2020. All Rights Reserved
Last update August 28, 2020
